(Penny:)You know, the only thing
worse than doing a movie
(Penny:)where they glue monkey hair
to your ass
(Penny:)is getting fired from a movie where
they glue monkey hair to your ass.
(Wil:)Forget it, man, it's crap.
You just move on to the next thing.
(Penny:)Yeah, well, it's easy for you to say.
You used to be famous.
(Wil:)Hey. I just lost a job for you.
(Howard:)You're right,
I'm sorry, you're famous.
(Wil:)Penny, it's not about being famous.
It's about the art.
(Wil:)It's about the passion
we have for our craft.
(Wil:)I have an audition
for Sharknadu 2!
(Wil:)If I book this, I am totally gonna
pay you back for this beer.
(Penny:)God, what am I doing with my life?
(Leonard:)You having second
thoughts about acting?
(Penny:)You were on set,
you saw what it was like.
(Leonard:)Yeah, but it's not always that bad.
(Penny:)Oh, really?
What about when you did Anne Frank
at that cute little theater
(Penny:)It was over a bowling alley.